[Music]
[Música]
let's put a little context on this
a ver pongo un poco en contexto de este
topic I haven't followed much about this topic
tema de este tema no lo he seguido mucho
but she's
pero me está
bringing me up to date karime tells me
me está poniendo al día karime me dice
juia's sister-in-law wife of this [ __ ]
la cuñada de juià esposa del tal bitches
lluvia's brother has always been a
hermano de lluvia siempre ha sido una
or it's said that she's always been a bit of a
o se dice que siempre ha sido un poco
stalker a stalker
acosador a una acosadora
remember that a while ago
recuerda que hace un tiempo se creó
fake accounts were created to harass juia and to
cuentas falsas para acosar a juià y para
self-stalk so today she contacted the
auto acosar se pues hoy contacto con la
baby rain fan account to
cuenta de fans del bebe de lluvia para
tell them that she has material that
decirles que tiene material que les
might interest them and she also offered
puede interesar y también ofreció
super exclusive material but in exchange
material súper exclusivo pero a cambio
for money it's supposed to be the
de dinero se supone que es la cuenta
real account I'll send you the story of this great one from
real te paso la historia de esta gran de
both accounts or even if that's true it
ambas cuentas o aun si eso es cierto
would be very serious let's see we would have these
sería muy grave a ver tendríamos estas
screenshots of people saying I'm going to do it
capturas de la gente diciendo se lo voy
alone from what I see no no it's false
a solito por lo que veo no no es falso
the person who uploaded it did it with
la persona que lo subió lo hizo con
video it's not just the screenshot and also
vídeo no es sólo la captura y ya además
paola has a strange way of doing
paola tiene una manera extraña de hacer
things it already happened to her a year ago when she
las cosas ya le pasó hace un año que se
went hey from her own account that's why
tiró hey desde su propia cuenta por eso
people noticed and coincidentally she
la gente se dio cuenta y casualmente se
disappeared for months
desapareció por meses
in  Instagram
en instagram
uploaded a video where it shows that
subió un vídeo donde según muestra que
the conversation is real and although Paola
es real la conversación y aunque paola
comes out to deny it obviously her past
salga a desmentir obviamente su pasado
supports her with her obsession with Julie
la respalda con su obsesión por julie
how scary and if I think she could charge
qué miedo y si creo que podría cargar
both times just like she did the
las dos veces así como lo hizo la
first time I don't think that after
primera vez no creo que después de que
no one from Juià's family wants Paola to have
nadie de la familia de juià quiera paola
done it again there my daughter doesn't
lo haya hecho otra vez hay mi hija no
learn I know what this will be
aprende yo sé que es este será el
Rain's brother the cycle is I know that you
hermano de lluvia el ciclo es yo sé que
love your wife but watch out here your
amas a tu esposa pero ojo aquí tu
sister and Marc baby is in danger with
hermana y marc bebé corre en peligro con
Paola next to them take it as advice
paola a un ladito tómalo como consejo
or rather
o sea se hace
the move would be made the move would be
la movida sería la movida sería
[Music]
[Música]
the move would be what
la movida sería qué
the dad the brother's wife
la papa la mujer del hermano
if she sleeps alone in fact let's see
si auto acostarse de hecho vamos a ver
a video here where
aquí un vídeo donde
[Music]
[Música]
where you can see no but to put it in
donde se ve no pero para ponerlo en
context okay this is about the past
contexto vale esto es sobre el pasado
this video and this video okay about the
este vídeo y este vídeo vale sobre el
past the video where I told you all the
pasado el vídeo donde les conté todo el
drama for Tito well I realized
drama por tito bueno pues me di cuenta
that many of you did not know the
que muchos de ustedes no sabían la
past controversy and they were
polémica pasada y me estuvieron
asking me to make this video
solicitando que les hiciera este vídeo
with all this information well I'll
con toda esta información bueno pues les
tell you how it all began  and all this
cuento cómo empezó todo y todo esto
started because there was an account that genes
empezó porque había una cuenta de genes
makes towards juià and the truth is that this
hace hacia juià y la verdad es que esta
account was very aggressive with her
cuenta era muy agresiva con ella
imagine so aggressive and to the
imagínense tan agresivos y hasta el
point that I already took action on the matter
grado que yo ya tomó cartas en el asunto
although we know that all the
si bien sabemos que todos los youtubers
influential youtubers well, it has to ingest it and
influences bueno pues tiene ingerir es y
normally xerez is very delicate
normalmente al xerez es muy delicado
when an account that is believed to
cuando sale una cuenta que se cree que
be anonymous comes out
es anónima
if you want to take legal action
si tú quieres tomar acciones legales
the police and the judges get in
la policía y los jueces se ponen en
touch with twitter
contacto con twitter
and twitter is forced we are going to force
y twitter está obligado vamos a obligado
us to give it the identity and all
nos lo hace a darle la identidad y todos
the data it has from that account is
los datos que tenga de esa cuenta es
totally localizable so well
localizable totalmente dio entonces
on that occasion they were haters
bueno pues en esa ocasión eran haters
too dedicated and they threw
demasiado dedicados y le tiraban
too much at her so imagine the level
demasiado entonces imagínense el nivel
of frustration and anger of lluvia that she
de frustración y de enojo de lluvia que
decided to investigate where this
decidió investigar de dónde venía esta
account came from when I and her
cuenta cuando yo ya y su equipo de
management team began to investigate well it is
management empezaron a investigar bueno
said that they found that the ip
pues se dice que encontraron que la ip
of the computer where it all came from that
de la computadora de dónde venía todo
well it was the same ip as
esa que bueno pues era la misma ip de la
pau's online address so at that
dirección de pau online entonces en ese
moment well I already discovered that
momento bueno pues yo ya descubrió que
all this game came from his
todo este game venía de parte de su
sister-in-law this well basically they were
cuñada esto pues básicamente eran
speculations and people were
especulaciones y la gente lo estaba
saying nothing was confirmed because
diciendo no era nada confirmado porque
up to that point I hadn't
hasta ese momento pues yo ya no había
kept anything and regarding payment and
conservado nada y por parte de pago y
deficit nothing has been said either
déficit pues tampoco se ha dicho nada
however like a month after they
sin embargo como un mes después de que
posted that post
pusieron ese post
I posted the following tweets what
yo ya puso los siguientes tweets que se
happens when you have to live by
hace cuando tienes que convivir a
force with someone you wouldn't like to see I
fuerzas con alguien que no te gustaría
swear I'm super tolerant but I can't stand
les juro que soy super tolerante pero no
double faced people and by
puedo con la gente de doble cara y para
that point I was already full for
ese momento yo ya estaba completo para
chairs and Beto for chairs posted the
sillas y beto para sillas puso a los
following what a disgrace to be close to
siguientes que desgracia ser cercano de
the most hypocritical and poisonous person in the
la persona más hipócrita y venenosa del
world and months later I posted this
mundo y meses después yo ya puso este
other tweet a few months ago something happened to me
otro tuit hace unos meses me pasó algo
that I never thought would happen to me friend
que jamás pensé que me pasaría amigo
someone very close to me was very evil
alguien muy cercana a mí era muy malvada
and Jordi doesn't matter and around that time
y jordi importa y por esas fechas se
the hashtag the sister-in-law
creó el hashtag del hashtag la cuñada
that nobody wants to have was created and in fact there are
que nadie quiere tener y de hecho
still tweets about it
todavía hay tweets al respecto
mother of god
madre de dios
mother of vido but why does
madre de vido pero por qué hace eso
Victor do that where she posted the following
víctor donde ella publicó el siguiente
tick tock jeanie buss piston harlow
tick tock jeanie buss piston harlow
genís mo
genís mo
this is the turkey
esta es la pava
whitman hipster obviously up to this
whitman hipster obviamente hasta este
point and everything is going well the text that
momento y va todo bien el texto que no
had nothing wrong with it until  that many
tenía nada de malo hasta que muchísimas
people but literally many people
personas pero literal muchas personas se
started to notice this little
empezaron a percatar de este pequeño
comment that said if you hate paola
comentario que decía si odias a paola
online follow us on insta I'm like
online síguenos en insta estoy como
digital universe well yes friends if you
universo digital pues sí amigos si no
are not understanding very well how pau
están entendiendo muy bien cómo que pau
manages an instagram account of lluvia
maneja una cuenta de instagram de lluvia
or that is what it implies and basically
o eso lo que da entender y básicamente
what happened was like she made a
lo que sucedió fue como que ella se
mistake and she forgot to change the
equivocó y se lo olvidó cambiar la
account to make this comment and she
cuenta para hacer este comentario y
commented from her main account
comentó de su cuenta principal
obviously many people including
obviamente muchísimas personas entre
brito youtuber or they realized
ellas o brito youtuber o se dieron
what was happening and
cuenta de lo que estaba sucediendo y
obviously they alerted the entire internet so
obviamente alertaron a todo internet así
basically in minutes all the
que básicamente en minutos ya todas las
people were realizing this
personas se estaban dando cuenta de este
tiny
pequeñísimo
huge mistake that she paid for
grandísimo error que pago
obviously the comments weren't
cometido obviamente los comentarios no
long in coming either and
tardaron en llegar tampoco a de las
people said like wrong and now
personas pusieron como que mal y ahora
the comment what a
el comentario
catch what a catch totally
vaya pillada vaya pillada total
[Music] let's
[Música]
upload a story let's go to the one who says
a subir una historia vamos al que dice
gangs I just want to tell you that I
pandillas solo quiero decirles que los
love you very much
quiero mucho
the move would be that the chick would
la movida sería que la pava
be offering something to a
le estaría ofreciendo algo a una cuenta
fan account of the baby of lluvia
fan del bebé de lluvia
man I imagine that she would not be
hombre yo me imagino que no le estaría
offering him the wrong or do not
ofreciendo la mal o no
tell us photos of the child video of  baby
nos hablan fotos del niño vídeo del bebé
something like that was being sold would
algo por el estilo se estaba vendiendo
n't they be selling any baby material
no estaría vendiendo algún material del
because it has been revived well it has been revived from what I
porque ha revivido pues ha revivido por
'm telling you find out is to
lo que te estoy diciendo entérate es al
pitas
pitas
the move would be that the chick would now
la movida sería que la pava ahora
be contacting fan accounts of the
estaría contactando con cuentas fans del
rain baby that already gives me the creeps in
bebé de lluvia que ya me da mal rollo de
itself that the baby has a fandom account
por sí que el bebé tenga cuenta fandom
okay and in exchange for money
vale y a cambio de dinero
this year my life changed a lot it
este año mi vida cambió muchísimo que
was a year of growth
fue un año de crecimiento
and don't believe everything you see
y que no crean todo todo lo que ven
because the truth is that many times
porque la verdad que muchas veces las
people have such bad temper
personas tiene una tan mala saña
and well none no way
y pues ninguno ni modo
the typical toxic 2 toxic thousand total total
la típica tóxica 2 tóxica mil total
given total but for me they have to
total dio total pero a mí a mí tienen
live with those things
que vivir con esas cosas
and this despite what they tell me you
y este a pesar de que me digan te
deserve many ugly things and things like that
mereces muchas cosas feas y cosas así
dzeko to the life of the universe goodbye that
dzeko a la vida del universo adiós que
right now everything is in its place and that I
ahorita todo esté en su lugar y que me
feel very happy with my family with
siento muy contenta con mi familia con
coquitos' family and with the
la familia de coquitos y con las
people who love me and I love like you
personas que me aman y amo como ustedes
Valeria god
valeria dios
is pregnant is pregnant is
está embarazada está embarazada está
pregnant can you do these things with
embarazada se puede hacer estas cosas de
little empathy to girls with little empathy
poca empatía a chicas que poca empatía
not even entering pregnant and this video that you
ni entrando embarazada y este vídeo que
send me like  the proof no the proof that it
me manda como la prueba no la prueba de
is a conversation no
que es una conversación no
hello hey I can help you by sending
hola oye yo te puedo ayudar mandando de
photos of the
fotos de
sea for you to publish just don't say
mar para que las publiques solo no digan
anything we can be a team what are you saying
nada podemos ser equipo que dices
or so this yes in Spain it would be a crime
o sea esto sí en españa sería delito
if someone imagined that someone in my
que alguien imaginaron que alguien de mi
family wants to send photos and videos of
familia quiera enviar fotos y vídeos de
my son
mi hijo
in exchange for money on top of that
a cambio de pasta encima
or
o
like a goat
como una cabra
here in Spain it would be totally possible done
aquí en españa sería totalmente posible
just don't say anything we can be teams what do you
sólo no digan nada podemos ser equipos
say I can also send you
que dices también puedo mandarte
private information about rain for
información privada sobre lluvia por
example I know the surgeries he has and
ejemplo se las cirugías que tiene y
where he had some done his address of his
donde se hizo alguna su dirección de su
mansion in Cuernavaca and the one in
mansión de cuernavaca y la de
Guadalajara although the information is private I
guadalajara aunque informa privada te la
can sell it to you if you want
puedo vender si quieres
gordon or
gordon o
this is already this
esto ya es esto ya
this is already a crime to
esto ya es delito
sell him the information
venderle la información
although even if he gives me latex to information
aunque aunque me de látex a información
that not only I have but also the
que no solo yo tengo sino también la
ridiculous fame and that they call themselves
ridícula fama y que se hacen llamar
cactus gers or their models of dancing
cactus gers o sus modelos de bailando
together that go to their house to do the
juntos que van a su casa a hacer las
sessions so think about it well can we
sesiones así que piénsalo bien podemos
be united or united what are you saying
estar unidos o unidas que dices
on top of that you have to be you have to think very
encima hay que ser hay que pensar bien
little no it's not for the money this is this it's
poquito no no es por la pasta es esto es
also for hate but you have to  think very
por odio también pero hay que pensar
little so they don't
bien poquito para que no te van a
expose you sending done
exponer mandando hecho
man
tío
[ __ ]
[__]
[Music]
[Música]
serious mental problem
problema mental grave
we put them, I no longer ended up like Selena
les ponemos yo ya no termine como selena
Quinta [ __ ] the case of Selena
quinta ostias el caso de selena
Quintanilla we were talking about him
quintanilla estuvimos hablando de él
recently in Julio her life takes you away
hace poco a julio su vida te aleja la de
Mar's if she takes care of you the series leaves her they choose her
mar si te cuida la serie deja la eligen
within the family a mentally ill person [ __ ]
dentro familia una enferma mental [__]
sincerely I am Rain's brother you have to
sinceramente yo soy el hermano de lluvia
be in love with the good one
ya tienes que estar enamorado del bueno
that's enough l
que baste l
what cake I would do before this is a
qué pastel que haría ante esto sea un
cake I did
pastelazo
not expect that this one becomes so good
no esperaba que éste se hace tan bueno
karime
karime
wow
wow
this is a crime in Mexico and
esto es delito en méxico y seguramente
they will surely sue
van a demandar
but it is very serious
pero es muy grave
[ __ ]
[__]
Fredette everyone's cake is
fredette el pastel de todos es el pastel
Rain's cake the brother's cake
de lluvia el pastel de el hermano
my goodness
madre mía
what a shame that people like that crazy
qué pena que a la gente así de loca
short trek a hug she knows the band
short trek un abrazo se la banda
looks she sends her to the army the theaters
mira se la manda al ejército los teatros
and being pregnant she thinks about her
y estando embarazada piensa en su
family totally
familia totalmente
[ __ ] how heavy
[__] qué heavy
what need with those followers that she
qué necesidad con esos seguidores que
has surely she has a lot of peace
tiene seguro que tiene un montón de paz
I know that she earns quite well
sé que gana bastante bien
[ __ ] man what need
[__] tío qué necesidad
toxicity at another level this has not
toxicidad a otro nivel esto ya no se ha
become criminal I mean it
hecho delictivo
's another  very low level dude
o sea es otro poquísimo nivel tío
let's save myself [ __ ] it's that they are already
salvemos a [__] es que ya se está
talking about issues of minors they
hablando de temas de menores
are already talking about putting and selling
se está hablando ya de poner y de vender
and negotiating with photos of minors guys
y de negociar con fotos de menores tíos
day [ __ ] day
día putísima día
look look the boyfriend he doesn't know it is look
mira mira el novio él no lo sabe es mira
your wife is crazy ten years together
tu esposa está loca diez años juntos
knowing how he has done to
sabiendo cómo es lo que le ha hecho a
yuya and yours a selfish so much that
yuya y tuya un interesado tanto que
profiting from the fight between both how bad
lucrarse con la pelea de ambas que mal
for both of them hating a person that
por ambos odiando a una persona que no
nobody knows and your own sister
la saben a nadie y a tu propia hermana
of kylie madness being the brother or uncle
de kylie locura ser el hermano o tío
what point soap opera
qué punto culebrón
is the typical bad girl of the soap opera
es la típica mala de la telenovela
wanting to sell the location of the
queriendo vender la ubicación de la
mansion in cuernavaca
mansión en cuernavaca
[ __ ] I laugh but the total laughter that I
[__] me río pero la risa total que
'm freaking out it's already very heavy it
estoy flipando ya es muy heavy
's very heavy god
es muy heavy dios
has seen it look has seen it
lo ha visto mirar lo ha visto
but how the [ __ ] do you dare to do something like that how the [ __ ] do you dare to do something
pero como [__] te atreves a hacer algo
like that does anyone know how the hell do
así
you dare to do something like that does
como [__] te atreves a hacer algo así
anyone know how to recover a message
alguien sabe cómo recuperar un mensaje
deleted by another person it's not possible
borrado por otra persona no se puede
impossible according to me instagram can
imposible según yo instagram puede
help in that aspect by reporting the
ayudar en ese aspecto al reportar la
conversation the messengers will know
conversación los mensajeros sabrán del
completely help me if it is deleted I
todo ayúdenme si se borra
wanted to delete a message sent to me
quería borrar mensaje me envió
friends I will not continue with  this gossip I will
amigos ya no seguiré con este chisme
leave everything in my featured stories
todo lo dejaré mi historias destacadas
but this account is not going to deviate it is its
pero esta cuenta no va a desviarse es su
main objective
objetivo principal
thanks catherine thank you very much
gracias catherine muchísimas gracias
welcome admire and want to love
bienvenida admirar y querer amar
anything that happens I will
cualquier cosa que pase yo se la
communicate it to those involved and I will not do
comunicaré a los involucrados y no haré
more gossip it is not healthy and besides the
más chismes no es sano y además la
account is not for that
cuenta no es para eso
karime today it takes it out on you or brutal friend I did not
karime hoy te la saca o amiga brutal no
expect this gossip it was so strong it is not
me esperaba este chisme era tan fuerte
gossip as such this is not this is not
no es un chisme como tal esto no es esto
gossip yes all this
no es un chisme si todo
was gossip site this is very
esto era un chisme sito esto es muy
strong and serious they are not deleted but to get it
fuerte y grave no se borran pero para
out you need
sacarlo necesitas criminalistas
informed criminalists that is deleted instagram if it
informada eso se borra instagram si los
deletes them whoever does not delete us twitter I think and I
borra el que no nos borra twitter creo y
think it does not have it for a few days
creo que tampoco lo tiene unos días
impossible has done well record the
imposible ha hecho bien grabar la
screen quickly
pantalla rápido
but this does not happen
pero esto no pasa
but these public messages like that man
pero estos mensajes públicos así hombre
sometimes they are publishing the messages as if
a veces están publicando los mensajes en
denouncing the complaint of a serious fact
denunciando la denuncia de un hecho
wow
guau
wow dall'anese a good on the stomach
wow dall'anese un bien sobre la tripa
like that it
así
is very strong and it is very strong it
es muy fuerte y es fuertísimo
is that I am imagining the
es que me estoy imaginando a
whole family with this brown arch
toda la familia con este marrón arco
imagine the whole family going through
imaginaros toda la familia pasando por
roca thank you very much
roca muchísimas gracias
all  the family with this ticket wow
toda la familia con esta papeleta
there are all kinds of people in the world
hay gente de todo tipo en el mundo
look at YouTube and surely a
fíjate de youtube y seguramente
millionaire
millonario
surely a millionaire boat me
seguramente millonario boat yo
wow
guau
[Music]
[Música]